Hello everyone
I'm Yueyang
Welcome to our 164th week of aesthetic training
This week, we're once again bringing you some poster works
We can learn by looking at designers from various countries
their creative ideas for posters
learn some new stylistic techniques
and at the same time enhance our own
a shift in mindset
Actually, for poster design
We can see that
Its presentation form is multifaceted.
We can draw from photography or realism
or from minimalist geometric shapes
including some typography
This method can actually be used.
It is not limited to a certain style
is the most aesthetically pleasing
Actually, we can see in the picture that
There's also this kind of simple and relaxed feeling
a picture book-like style
there are also these relatively simple and concise graphics
a concise and flat style
Of course, there are also many such illustration styles
They are actually all about the object we need to express
or the theme being expressed
and then present this technique
I think in our daily design work,
may come into contact with relatively less
because our poster aesthetic training
mostly still with a focus on foreign posters, huh
There are also some domestic ones
Why focus more on foreign designs?
Actually, because we live in this environment ourselves,
We definitely tend to see more things from our own country
At this point, certain limitations tend to emerge
It's not that the posters we make are bad.
It's not that we're doing this aesthetic training
is actually about broadening one's horizons
I think this is very important
because our techniques
expression techniques or application methods
the more diverse the presentation methods of design are
it will also provide us with more directions for future projects
we also have more directions for consideration
not overly constrained
For designers as well,
We also need to continuously improve our aesthetic sense
including improving one's skills
I think this is a very important part
Of course, while improving skills at the same time
It's not about always making your work overly complex
very very annoying
a very complicated state
I don't think this state is necessarily correct.
Because you have to think about simplifying complexity, right
When we reach a certain level of complexity,
We need to learn how to make some reductions
adopt a more modest approach
including the Japanese designs we see today
it is actually achieved through this kind of minimalist
a relatively simple style to present
The theme includes our Chinese painting
In fact, it employs a substantial amount of negative space in its design, alright
Actually, we can observe the Space of the posters
this size relationship
Take these posters for example
They are, um, not all that intricate in terms of graphics, right
It's just a few simple graphics or very few colors
just two colors like this
Two colors can also make it rich and colorful
This requires us to pay attention to the text
Space
including this modeling
theme
see how you create this sense of atmosphere
this kind of atmospheric element
It's not something we can achieve all at once.
We may need to observe more
after watching
we then apply it to our actual projects
we can then achieve a great state
Of course, I think now
including our overall design direction now
are all trending towards a more abstract
a relatively simple style
similar to this Picasso-like feeling, right
So in this modern era,
We are also the same
some often simple and aesthetically pleasing things
I think we should observe more often.
including some of the small things around us
these small graphic patterns
Actually, they can bring us a lot of inspiration
including some test composition graphics
Hey
This and that combined form another shape
I think this is quite an interesting thing
It often can have a very good presentation.
It can also attract people
including this kind of playful typesetting
overlapping, right
including combining two different things together
These are also some things we need to think about.
How to make your work more fun and interesting
fun and playful
That concludes our 164th week of aesthetic training
Thank you for watching
See you next time